[Music]
[音乐]
all right welcome to the to the session
好的，欢迎参加会议
everybody the the cool container
大家很酷的容器
revisited part of this is really a bit
再来看看这部分确实
of a revealing the focus we're going to
揭示我们将要关注的重点
look at Spring Framework five the two
看一下Spring Framework的五个二
from a very specific perspective cool
从非常特定的角度来看很酷
mechanisms that we had to revisit Co
我们不得不重新审查的机制
abstractions that we had to revisit in
我们必须重新审视的抽象
the five to two timeframe with a strong
五到两个时间框架
motivation from high up the stack from
动力来自高处
certain usage models from spring boot
Spring Boot的某些使用模型
from a spring data in particular in this
特别是从弹簧数据中
this particular release so there was
这个特定的版本，所以有
quite a bit of of requirements coming
相当多的需求即将到来
down from other portfolio projects down
低于其他投资组合项目
to the core framework to the co
到公司的核心框架
container and I'm going to take this
容器，我要拿这个
opportunity to reveal some of our of the
机会揭示我们的一些
changes that we made the motivation
我们动机的变化
behind them
在他们后面
since there's quite a bit that has been
因为已经有很多
introduced in 5.1 as well and I suppose
我也认为是在5.1中引入的
most if you are very aware of what five
如果您非常了解五个
did oh did but not as aware of what came
哦，但没有意识到
in 5.1 I'm also for for the initial part
在5.1中，我也开始学习
of this presentation for the first part
本演示文稿的第一部分
I'm going to take the opportunity to
我将借此机会
discuss a few key design changes design
讨论一些关键的设计变更设计
elements that we introduced in 5.1 first
我们首先在5.1中引入的元素
and we're going into very five to two
我们将要进入​​五到两个
specific mechanisms right afterwards so
事后有特定的机制
this is of course very close to my
这当然非常接近我
everyday work since I I'm in charge of
因为我负责日常工作
managing the Spring Framework project
管理Spring框架项目
quite a bit of the work that we did here
我们在这里所做的很多工作
is literally happening as we speak here
我们在这里说话时确实发生了
in in my hands and in my team so this is
在我和我的团队中，所以这是
very hot from the oven be aware that
烤箱很热，要注意
this is work in progress five to two is
这是正在进行的工作，五到两个是
approaching a third milestone it's not
接近第三个里程碑不是
in the release candidate phase yet most
在候选发布阶段
of the features that we discussing here
我们在这里讨论的功能
are already available either in 5.1 or
在5.1或
in five to two
五到二
to some of them and I'm going to point
对其中的一些，我要指出
them out I hope you don't forget I'm
他们出来，我希望你不要忘记我
going to point them out are only coming
指出他们只会来
in m3 or in our c1 so I still are not
在m3或我们的c1中，所以我仍然不
actually released yet so let's go down
实际发布了，所以让我们下去
to the core api's and as you are
到核心api的原样
certainly aware Spring Framework 5 todo
当然知道Spring Framework 5要做的事情
came as an opportunity for us the Java 8
对我们来说是一个机会Java 8
baseline allowed us to literally revisit
基线使我们能够重新审视
the entire code base in particular the
整个代码库，特别是
entire API surface the language elements
整个API展示了语言元素
the design capabilities of the Java 8
Java 8的设计能力
language elements are really shining
语言元素真的很闪亮
through here and we were able to revisit
通过这里，我们能够重新访问
a lot of the API surface from the
许多API表面
perspective of Java 8 streams of course
Java 8流的观点
from the perspective of using lambdas
从使用lambdas的角度
and functional interfaces there's a lot
和功能界面很多
of impact that it had and it keeps
产生并保持的影响
having an impact refining Java 8 API
具有影响力的Java 8 API
design is kind of a it's it's its
设计是一种它的
ongoing work that is still with us
正在进行的工作仍在我们身边
there are refinements coming in five to
有五项改进
two still along that theme but let's
两个仍然沿着这个主题，但让我们
let's just pick up a few central
让我们来接几个中央
elements from that story the the first
那个故事的元素，第一个
time that we were ever able to use Java
我们曾经能够使用Java的时间
8 API types in our own API sand SPS was
我们自己的API sand SPS中的8种API类型是
bring from at 500 but we only did an
从500带来，但我们只做了
initial pass through the code base a lot
最初通过代码库的次数很多
of follow up came in 5.1 and it
跟进是在5.1中
manifests in many ways it's in
以多种方式体现出来
particular the use of Java 8 API types
特别是Java 8 API类型的使用
as well not just language elements so
不仅是语言元素
it's about for example the new time
例如关于新时间
types local date time and so forth it's
输入本地日期时间，依此类推
about the use of completable future
关于使用可完成的未来
introduced in Java 8 there's some more
Java 8中引入了更多功能
efficient reflection lookups we can do
我们可以做的高效反射查找
with the use of executable a new base
使用可执行文件的新基础
class of constructor method introduced
构造函数方法类介绍
in Java 8 there's quite a few things
在Java 8中，有很多事情
that of course the Java util streams
当然是Java util流
that we that we introduced on that
我们在那介绍的
opportunity the other part that we did
机会，我们所做的另一部分
and this is also still very much with us
这对我们来说仍然非常重要
with
与
refining the interfaces for the use of
完善接口以供使用
default methods so if you've already
默认方法，所以如果您已经
closely integrated with some of the
与某些
interfaces in springform at 500 and 5-1
springform中的接口在500和5-1
you might have noticed that default
您可能已经注意到默认
methods keep appearing we are really
方法不断出现，我们确实
clearing in particular existing methods
特别清除现有方法
as default methods so that you as an
作为默认方法，这样您就可以
implement of the interface or some
接口的实现或某些
integrators as implementers of the
集成商是实施者
interface having an easier time it this
界面拥有更轻松的时间
is in particular relevant for the
与...特别相关
callback interfaces so if you customize
回调接口，因此如果您自定义
say beam post processing or handler
说光束后处理或处理程序
method interceptors in spring MVC then
然后在Spring MVC中使用方法拦截器
those are easier to implement now since
这些现在更容易实现，因为
the methods are all default methods and
这些方法都是默认方法，
you just choose to implement the one you
您只是选择实施一个
really care about so that this all comes
真的很在乎这一切
as a consequence of the Java eight
由于Java八
baseline another related effort that we
建立基线，这是我们的另一项相关努力
went through is the null ability story
经历过的是零能力的故事
and I've been referring to it this
我一直在指这个
morning mostly as a follow-up there's
早上主要是跟进
there's a follow-up effort a
有后续工作
collaboration with Google and JetBrains
与Google和JetBrains合作
so the for for a better defined that a
所以为了更好地定义
well defined that properly released meta
定义明确，正确发布的meta
notation model behind this but in
背后的符号模型
essence the story is very immediate in
本质上，这个故事是非常直接的
our API design the entire API surface
我们的API设计了整个API表面
comes with cleanability declarations
附带清洁声明
it's basically a form of null safe API
它基本上是null安全API的一种形式
design we declare our packages to be non
设计，我们声明我们的包装不是
null by default exceptions to the rule
默认情况下为null
meaning arguments that can be inaudible
意思是听不清的参数
return values that can be null are
可以为null的返回值是
explicitly annotated as such so if you
如此明确地注释，如果您
look at even just the Java doc or the
甚至只看Java文档或
API in the IDE if you're calling say
IDE中的API（如果您要说）
bean factory gets been you've got a
豆工厂得到你有一个
clear contract that the incoming
明确合同
parameters are usually not expected to
通常不期望参数
be null and more importantly even that
为null，更重要的是
the return values are usually non null
返回值通常不为null
guaranteed to be not null you may rely
保证您不依赖于null
on this if they can be null we annotate
在此如果它们可以为null，则我们进行注释
the method with nullable meaning that
具有可空含义的方法
the return value of that particular
该特定商品的返回值
method can be null this is a formal
方法可以为null，这是形式上的
declaration that we're validating
我们正在验证的声明
with some use of tooling in IntelliJ
在IntelliJ中使用一些工具
IDEA this great support for this both in
IDEA为此提供了极大的支持
life editing and also in terms of the
生活编辑以及
inspections that you can run against the
您可以针对
codebase we do that internally to make
代码库，我们在内部做
sure that our pretty large code base has
确保我们的大型代码库具有
clean malleability code paths so that
清除可延展性代码路径，以便
all the assumptions that we make about
我们所做的所有假设
something being null or non null I
东西为空或非空我
actually valid down to the down the
实际上有效到了
entire call stack you can do the same in
整个调用堆栈，您可以在
your applications
您的申请
with our api s-- being shipped with
与我们的api一起发货
those annotations you may have code of
那些您可能具有以下代码的注释
yours application code calling into the
您的应用程序代码调用
spring api's and you may use for example
春天的API，你可以使用例如
IntelliJ is tooling IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ是IntelliJ IDEA的工具
tooling to validate your calls into our
工具来验证您对我们的呼叫
methods the tooling is simply making use
工具使用的简单方法
of these formal declarations that we we
在这些正式声明中，我们
ship through those nullable annotations
通过这些可为空的注释发送
the effect on coding is of course even
当然，对编码的影响甚至
stronger because in Kotlin there's a an
更强大，因为在科特林有一个
element of non-enforcement in the type
类型中不执行的元素
system you can declare a type references
系统可以声明类型引用
not null and the coupling compiler is
不为null，耦合编译器为
going to allow such an assignment only
只允许这样的分配
if the outcome of the call of the
如果呼叫的结果
expression that you assign is cleanly
您分配的表达式是干净的
not null so if you call any API with
不为null，因此如果您使用
unclear null ability this thing maybe
不清楚null能力这个东西也许
not the cutting compiler is going to
不是切割编译器要
reject the immediate assignment whereas
拒绝立即分配，而
if you're calling a spring API method
如果您正在调用spring API方法
which is cleanly declare to be non null
明确声明为非null
the cutting compiler is going to happily
切割编译器会很高兴
allow the assignments this is one of the
允许作业，这是其中之一
reasons why we did this not only for the
我们之所以这样做的原因不仅在于
Java tooling which is nice in particular
Java工具特别好
for the interaction with the cutting
与切割互动
compiler which is really quite an
编译器真的很
important enabler in a in our cutting
在我们切割中的重要推动力
story all right and here's a just a few
故事还好，这里只是几个
examples and a little bit of new API
示例和一些新的API
shining through a good example is our
通过一个很好的例子闪耀是我们的
object provider which is reasonably
合理的对象提供者
recent for three introduced but as of
最近推出了三款，但截至
5.1 it's also available with a
5.1还可与
programmatic call on the application
对应用程序进行编程调用
context on the bean factory get beam
Bean工厂的上下文获取光束
provider and the type that you're
提供者和您的类型
interested in
有兴趣
we'll give you an object provider of
我们会给您一个对象提供者
that type of a foo here and the object
此处的foo类型和对象
provider has several methods and just
提供者有几种方法，只是
look at the null ability get if
看空能力得到如果
available in terms of its semantics says
就其语义而言可用
give me the object if it's present in
如果存在的话给我
the context if it's not return now write
如果不返回上下文，现在写
the same forget if unique if there's a
同样忘记如果有
unique object just a single one matching
唯一的对象只有一个匹配
the type give it to me otherwise return
类型给我，否则返回
now those methods of course declared as
现在这些方法当然声明为
nullable the return value is nullable
可返回值可为空
some new methods that we introduced in
我们在其中引入了一些新方法
that was back in FIFO being providers
回到FIFO成为提供者
5/1 these methods have have a bit of a a
5/1这些方法有点AA
play with the null ability basically
基本上可以发挥零能力
they have a bit of a twist in them get
他们有一点曲折
if available and here is a Java util
如果可用，这是一个Java util
function supplier returning a default
功能提供者返回默认值
value if it's not available means that
值（如果不可用）表示
the return value is guaranteed to be non
返回值保证为非
null either it's an object from the
null要么是来自
context or it's the object that if that
上下文或对象，如果那
the default supplier produces and the
默认供应商生产，
default suppliers usually bound with a
默认供应商通常会绑定
Java 8 lambda expression or with a Java
Java 8 Lambda表达式或Java
8 method reference or even a little bit
8方法参考甚至一点
more functional to say like if it's
更具功能性地说
available
有空
here's a consumer to do something with
这是一个可以做某事的消费者
the object if it's available if it's not
对象，如果不可用则可用
available just skip the call so we have
可用，只需略过通话即可
a few API methods that really make sense
一些真正有意义的API方法
if you compare the inaudible handling
如果您比较听不清处理
where they are explicitly designed to
它们被明确设计为
avoid null return values in their
避免在他们的空返回值
semantics and nullable declarations make
语义和可为空的声明使
this very explicit not hidden in the
这个非常明确的没有隐藏在
Java doc it's right there in the
Java文档就在其中
signature if you take the annotations
如果带注释，请签名
into account 5-1 also allows us to do a
考虑到5-1还使我们能够
little bit more with the object provider
对象提供者多一点
if you have it by the way object
如果您有顺便说一句
provider can be programmatically
提供者可以通过编程
resolved with the get pin provider call
通过get pin provider调用解决
but as shown above
但如上所述
it can also be injected into your
也可以注入到您的
component if you just say instead of at
组件，如果您只是说而不是在
auto wired foo add auto white object
自动有线foo添加自动白色对象
provider of foo then you have this
foo的提供者，那么您有这个
indirection handle in your hands that's
在您手中的间接句柄
what we will inject into your component
我们将注入您的组件中的内容
for more sophisticated lei
对于更复杂的林雷
easy resolution of the object when you
您轻松分辨对象
need it so it's not an immediate
需要它，所以它不是立即的
reference of food it's a handle to
食物的参考
retrieve a through a particular instance
通过特定实例检索
of food if you need it
如果需要的话
and aside from from the methods we were
除了我们以前的方法
just discussing the availability and
只是讨论可用性和
uniqueness methods there's a few further
唯一性方法还有更多
ones in 5.1 in particular for multiple
5.1中的那些特别针对多个
matching objects so if there may be more
匹配的对象，所以如果还有更多
than one such such being implementing
比这样的实施
the full interface in your in your
您中的完整界面
context then you can iterate over those
上下文，然后您可以遍历那些
you can build a Java util stream over
您可以通过构建Java util流
those both of them does it they
他们俩都做到了
basically lazily resolving as far as
基本上懒惰地解决
possible there's also an ordered stream
可能还有一个有序的流
with spring at order semantics take me
带着春天的命令语义带我
into accounts across the matching
进入匹配项中的帐户
instances in the application context so
在应用程序上下文中的实例
some pretty sophisticated retrieval
一些相当复杂的检索
interaction with the container that we
与我们的容器互动
are enabling this way some oldie but
正在通过这种方式使一些老歌，但
goodie before we move on this goes
好东西，我们继续前进
really nicely with the which is the bean
真的很好用哪个是豆子
methods that we introduced in FIFO so
我们在FIFO中介绍的方法
the the retrieval side of it the stuff
它的检索方面
shown here basically the the
基本上显示在这里
programmatic interaction programmatic
程序交互
retrieval against the container goes
针对容器进行检索
really nicely with programmatic
程式辅助非常好
registration of the beans it's actually
实际注册的咖啡豆
independent you can programmatically
您可以通过编程独立
retrieve components that are declared
检索声明的组件
through the eight computer through 8
通过八台计算机通过8
configuration classes and you can of
配置类，您可以
course do annotation based injection of
当然做基于注解的
components that you register
您注册的组件
programmatically it's all mixing and
以编程方式将所有内容混合在一起
matching
匹配
but stylistically it goes together very
但从风格上讲
nicely so this is just snippets of how
很好，这只是如何
you can programmatically reduce the
您可以以编程方式减少
components in a functional style s
功能样式的组件
offspring from AK 5 to though so if you
从AK 5到后代
there's a little bit of use of new is in
有一些新的使用
there registering a a component of type
在那里注册一个类型的组件
foo a bean definition for that component
foo该组件的bean定义
will be registered underneath the covers
将在封面下注册
and one for bar and the bar one comes
一个是酒吧，另一个是酒吧
with an instant supplier that is
与即时供应商
building a new bar instance and calls
建立一个新的酒吧实例并调用
back to the container to retrieve an
回到容器中
instance of food that is to be
食物的实例
injected into it over here the the
在这里注入
example below is a little bit more
下面的例子多一点
sophisticated because it registers the
复杂，因为它注册了
bar components with an instant supplier
即时供应商的钢筋组件
that doesn't inject foo itself it makes
它本身不会注入foo
use of the new get in provider method in
使用新的get in provider方法
five one you pass a an object provider
五，你通过一个对象提供者
of foo into that bar constructor and Bar
foo进入该bar构造函数和Bar
can lazily interact with the container
可以懒惰地与容器互动
to retrieve the actual for instance and
检索实际的实例和
beyond that it additionally reaches thus
除此之外，它因此达到
the underlying marks the underlying ping
底层标志底层ping
definition is lazy in it so if it's a
定义是懒惰的，所以如果它是一个
singleton by default it will even the
默认情况下，单例甚至
bar instance itself will only be created
bar实例本身只会被创建
as some other component retrieves a bar
当其他组件检索条形图时
from the container so this is an
来自容器，所以这是一个
alternative to configuration classes in
替代配置类
the end entirely programmatic
完全以编程方式结束
no reflection involved no annotations
没有反射，没有注释
involved going really nicely together
在一起真的很融洽
with paramedic retrieval so this is the
与医护人员检索，所以这是
Copeland version of it we're not going
我们不会去的谷轮版
to go into it in much detail but keep in
对其进行详细介绍，但要保留
mind in spring for Mach 5 we keep
在春天，我们会继续保持5马赫的速度
shipping cotton extensions they are
运输棉花扩展他们
actually seriously refined over v 1 and
实际上在v 1和
v 2 as well there's a there's in
v 2也有一个
particular a nice little almost dsl like
特别是一个不错的一点几乎像DSL一样
experience that you can get out of the
您可以摆脱的体验
combination of coupling language
耦合语言的组合
features and our Kotlin being
功能和我们的Kotlin被
registration to yourself there's no
向自己注册没有
special set of necessary just choose to
特殊的必要设置只是选择
use Coplin use a spring context 5 105 to
使用Coplin使用spring上下文5 105
jar and start using those methods they
jar并开始使用这些方法
are delivered as cotton extensions
作为棉花扩展交付
coming in the standard jars the cotton
在标准罐子里放棉花
compiler automatically picks them up and
编译器自动将它们拾取并
applies them to the spring api types by
将它们应用于spring api类型
convention so that you can have a very
约定，以便您可以拥有一个非常
nice out-of-the-box experience this code
开箱即用的好代码
is basically doing almost the same as
基本上与
the code before it's just different
之前的代码有所不同
twists down there with the inline which
用内联线向下扭曲
is the being calls for a more dsl like
是被要求像
experience and up there with the the
经验和在那里
inline instant supplier there's a bit of
在线即时供应商有一些
a convenience that comes out of Kopplin
Kopplin带来的便利
because we can use dedicated copy and
因为我们可以使用专用副本
reflection AP is also something we've
反射AP也是我们要做的事情
been recently introducing and
最近介绍了
enforcing that there is as there's as
强制存在
little repetition as technically
从技术上讲很少重复
possible in Java we have to ask for
在Java中可能我们必须要求
explicit in types in some cases because
在某些情况下是明确的类型，因为
we can't infer the return types of
我们无法推断出的返回类型
lender expressions and method references
贷方表达式和方法参考
whereas in Kotlin there's a dedicated
而在科特林有一个专门的
reflection api with a reliable return
具有可靠回报的反射API
type inferred so you can have a really
推断类型，这样您就可以
nice shortcut syntax in this case for
在这种情况下，不错的快捷方式语法
registering the bar component where we
在我们注册酒吧组件的地方
don't have to say borrowed class and
不必说借来的课和
here's how to create it the supplier
这是创建供应商的方法
itself the one Thea
本身就是一个Thea
did this little snippet of code that
做了这小段代码
creates an instance of bar reliably
可靠地创建bar的实例
tells us that it will be a bar class
告诉我们这将是一个酒吧课
after all so it's just for a little bit
毕竟，这只是一点点
of coupling in here let's move on to a
耦合在这里，让我们继续
particular five to two topic performance
特别是五到两个主题的表现
tuning we have several efforts that I
调优，我们有一些努力，我
would summarize on the performance
将总结表现
tuning it's mostly about startup
调整主要是关于启动
optimizations
优化
but it's as always read in any form of
但它一如既往地以任何形式
performance improvements you never
从未有过的性能提升
really done we are trying to optimize
确实完成了，我们正在尝试优化
according to the feedback that we get
根据我们得到的反馈
according to our own understanding of
根据我们自己的理解
the trade-offs that we we make this is a
我们进行的权衡是一个
totally non-trivial effort
完全不费吹灰之力
are you optimizing for startup time are
您在优化启动时间吗
you optimizing for peak performance
您针对峰值性能进行了优化
there's often iterator if you have to
如果需要，通常会有迭代器
make are you optimizing for single
让你为单身优化
threaded execution or for highly
线程执行或高度
concurrent execution these things do not
并发执行这些事情不
always are not all achievable already we
总是不是所有人都可以实现的
have to make a certain trade-off between
必须在两者之间做出一定的权衡
those optimizations for five to two our
这些优化需要五到两个
focus was primarily on our starter
主要关注我们的入门者
performance allow spring based
性能允许基于弹簧
applications to be designed in a way
以某种方式设计应用程序
where they start up as quickly as
他们尽快开始
possible at the expense of some of the
可能以牺牲一些
initial requests coming in possibly
最初的请求可能会出现
taking a little bit longer than before
花费比以前更长的时间
but at least the the system itself is
但是至少系统本身是
present accessible monitor able a little
目前可访问的显示器能够一点点
bit earlier there's there's several
有点早，有几个
facets to it and I'm taking the
方面，我正在
opportunity to discuss a few of them
有机会讨论其中的一些
what one of them is annotation
其中之一是注释
processing
处理中
in it in our efforts to optimize what we
在努力优化我们的工作中
call merged annotations and merged
调用合并的注释并合并
annotation processing we are we arrived
批注处理我们到了
in five to two at the decision to
决定以五到二
completely reinvent the underlying
彻底重塑底层
annotation handling so 5 to 2 comes with
注释处理，因此5至2
basically a a new implementation of
基本上是一个新的实现
annotation processing rewritten from the
注释处理从
ground up but hidden behind the same API
从头开始，但隐藏在同一个API后面
so existing code using annotation utils
所以现有的代码使用注释工具
or annotated element details would still
或带注释的元素详细信息仍
work fine
做工不错
binary with binary compatibility but
具有二进制兼容性的二进制文件，但
actually uses the new mechanism the new
实际上使用新机制
facility under under the covers what we
掩护下的设施
call merged annotations is a Springs
称合并注解为Springs
particular way of of allowing composed
允许组成的特定方式
annotations if you've ever wondered how
注解，如果您曾经想过
we process these things like a rest
我们像休息一样处理这些事情
controller being an annotation called
控制器是一个称为
rest controller but having an earth
休息控制器，但有一个土壤
controller annotation and a net response
控制器注释和净响应
body annotation as a meta annotation on
身体注释作为元注释
the annotation type discomposing of
注释类型分解
annotations through annotating the
通过注释来注释
annotation what we call meta annotations
注解我们称为元注解
this is what we're calling merged
这就是我们所说的合并
annotation processing and doing this
注释处理并执行此操作
efficiently is quite non-trivial so five
有效地是不平凡的，所以五个
to two is basically a our way to revisit
基本上两个是我们重新审视的方式
the arrangement and an important part of
的安排和重要组成部分
it is allowing for expressing hints for
它允许表达提示
optimizing shortcutting wherever
随时随地优化快捷方式
possible if there are no annotations to
如果没有注释，则可能
be found on a particular component type
在特定的组件类型上找到
we don't need to go searching through it
我们不需要去搜索它
we don't even need to reflectively look
我们甚至不需要反思
at its methods if we know that no such
如果我们知道没有这样的方法
annotations are to be found there anyway
无论如何都可以在这里找到注释
reflection can be expensive it doesn't
反射可能会很昂贵，但不会
have to be but reflective scanning of
必须是但必须进行反射扫描
the signature of classes can be somewhat
类的签名可能有点
expensive in particular on startup so
特别是在启动时很昂贵，所以
there's the motion annotations API is
有运动注释API是
already in 5 to 2 m2 coming up in m3 or
已经在5到2平方米之间，或者在3平方米内
the latest in our see one is some form
我们看到的最新形式是某种形式
of an annotation presence registry more
注释存在注册表的更多信息
importantly an annotation absence
重要的是没有注释
registry where basically if if you know
注册表在哪里，如果你知道的话
that certain certain classes of your so
您的某些特定类别
component types or even certain packages
组件类型甚至某些软件包
of yours whatever it is if you know that
无论您是什么，如果您知道
there is no such annotation to be found
找不到这样的注释
in there you should be able to register
在那儿你应该能够注册
a hint with the runtime system that we
运行时系统的提示
don't even need to bother looking at
甚至不需要打扰
those types for those particular
那些特殊的类型
annotations so in its simplest form you
注释，以最简单的形式
would just say like I know that on this
只会说我知道
particular class only those annotation
特定的类只有那些注释
types are ever to be found and by simply
可以找到类型，并且只需
expressing this in a one-line
单行表达
programmatic call the container would
以编程方式调用容器
skip the entire search for any other
跳过整个搜索
annotation types on those classes this
这些类上的注释类型
can be the intent for it this is not
可以为此目的不是
actually shifting them to it the intent
实际上将他们转移到它的意图
for it is to allow you to express those
因为它是为了让你表达那些
hints wherever you get them from you can
提示，无论您从何处获得
programmatically register those before
以编程方式注册之前的人
bootstrapping but in particular you
自举，但特别是你
could take a sum index information if
可以获取总和索引信息，如果
you happen to have any and translate it
你碰巧有任何翻译
onto this annotation registry before you
移至此注解注册表之前
bootstrap Oh at a very early phase of
在很早的阶段就进行引导
bootstrapping so if you happen to have
引导，所以如果你碰巧有
for example H and X index that your
例如H和X索引
built produces where information about
内置产生有关
the annotation types on the components
组件上的注释类型
is actually in there you could choose to
实际上在那里，您可以选择
parse that index on startup extract
在启动提取时解析该索引
annotation information and apply it to
注释信息并将其应用于
Springs annotation processing
弹簧标注处理
infrastructure when you then bootstrap
引导时的基础架构
the spring application context it would
春天的应用程序上下文
make use of those immediate annotation
利用这些即时注释
hints instead of having to reflectively
提示，而不必反思
introspect all your classes the details
内省所有课程的详细信息
of how exactly you would express
你将如何表达
yourself here are still to be decided on
你自己在这里还有待决定
we want to allow integration with
我们想允许与
indexes from a core framework
核心框架中的索引
perspective we are not going to ship
观点，我们不会发货
out-of-the-box integration with indexes
与索引的现成集成
with particular index arrangements it's
与特定的索引安排
more of an integration point with
与更多的集成点
indexes that a particular application
索引特定的应用程序
arrangement could make use of so it's
安排可以利用，所以
opening up a core mechanism for external
对外开放的核心机制
metadata for external information from
来自外部信息的元数据
an index to be fed into it before
之前要输入的索引
bootstrapping
自举
another interesting topic that I'd like
我想要的另一个有趣的话题
to discuss for for just a bit picking up
讨价还价
again on something I raced this morning
再次参加今天早上我参加的比赛
a grouse VM native images this is of
一个松散的VM本机映像
course very closely attached to the this
当然与此紧密相关
theme that I outlined before trading off
我在权衡之前概述的主题
startup time for peak performance that
达到最佳性能的启动时间
is basically and then trading off a
基本上是然后权衡
reduced memory consumption for peak
减少峰值内存消耗
performance this is pretty much growl
性能，这几乎是咆哮
VMs elevator pitch at least substrate
VM升降机至少倾斜基板
VMs elevator pitch so the the growl vm
虚拟机电梯间距使咆哮的虚拟机
native image mechanism keep in mind that
本机映像机制请记住
this is experimental at all levels even
这在所有层面上都是实验性的
the recent GA release of corral vm
畜牧vm的最新GA版本
problem 19 GA does not actually ship and
问题19 GA并未实际发货，
the native image support in in
中的本机图像支持
production ready form you have to do an
生产准备表，你必须做一个
extra installation step to even get it
额外的安装步骤甚至得到它
and it's it's labeled as a kind of early
它被标记为一种早期
adopter i kind of develop a preview
采纳者，我有点开发预览
mechanism at this point so anything we
在这一点上的机制，所以我们
do of course is just as experimental but
当然是实验性的，但是
it's it's it's quite interesting we did
这是我们做的很有趣
a little bit of revision last year
去年做了一些修改
already where we're trying to avoid
已经在我们试图避免的地方
unnecessary reflection points within the
内的不必要的反射点
code base like spi level in sensation of
像spi级别的代码库
defaults growl vm is very capable of
默认情况下，grol vm非常有能力
handling reflection if you instructed
如果您指示，请处理反射
with reflecting reflection configuration
具有反射反射配置
with certain configuration rules of what
与什么的某些配置规则
it needs to do when you wedding and
婚礼时需要做的
count a certain certain reflection
算一定的反思
points of which classes it needs to be
需要的是哪一类
capable of delivering reflection
能够反射
information for reflection metadata for
反射元数据的信息
but we are trying to minimize the amount
但是我们正在努力减少数量
of metadata it needs there through some
它需要通过一些元数据
internal little refactorings where we're
内部小重构
trying to be growl friendly within the
试图在
code base at this point in 5 to 2 we
此时的代码库为5比2
went quite far with just prototyping our
仅用原型制作就走了很远
way through the combination of spring
弹簧组合方式
form of 5 to 2 on Angra on substrate vm
基质vm上Angra上5到2的形式
using native images the amount of
使用本地图像的数量
explicit configuration can still be a
显式配置仍然可以
little challenging now
现在有点挑战
there's only certain configurations of
只有某些配置
corral and of spring based systems that
畜栏和基于弹簧的系统
really work but rest assured here that
确实有效，但请放心
there is no conflict between Brad VM
Brad VM之间没有冲突
assumptions and like a fundamental
假设和基本
conflict between rowdy M assumptions and
粗略的M假设与
spring programming model elements
弹簧编程模型元素
there's just a little extra
有一点点额外
configuration needed to make the
进行配置所需的配置
configuration work and towards five to
配置工作，并朝着五
three we're trying to get towards some
三个我们正在努力走向一些
kind of out-of-the-box set up the
开箱即用的设置
details have yet to be seen but it's
细节尚未发现，但是
already been prototype that this is
已经是原型，这是
totally possible that we would create
我们完全有可能创造
the corresponding RAL reflection
相应的RAL反射
configuration on deployment of a
部署时的配置
particular spring application so that
特殊的弹簧应用，以便
the grouse VM finds all the metadata
松鸡VM找到所有元数据
necessary for your application
您的应用程序必需的
components when when creating the native
创建本机时的组件
image and the native image then contains
图片，然后本机图片包含
all the relevant class information so
所有相关的班级信息
that the framework then in this native
那框架就在这个原生的
image when deployed as a native image as
作为本地映像部署时的映像
part of a native image can use its usual
本机映像的一部分可以使用其通常的
reflection api's to get the metadata
反射API获取元数据
needed at runtime so there's a few rough
在运行时需要，所以有一些粗糙
patches of course still as you would
当然仍然像您一样修补
expect there to be we compiled the
期望有我们编译
current state of affairs into the this
目前的状况
github link down there it's a wiki page
github链接在那里，这是一个Wiki页面
where the current state of our
我们当前的状态
understanding of the latest Spring
了解最新的春天
Framework generation the latest problem
框架生成的最新问题
releases is going to be maintained so
版本将被维护，因此
there's currently a reflection of the
目前有一种反映
state of the art as of as of this week
截至本周为止的技术水平
and we intend to update this wiki page
我们打算更新这个维基页面
whenever new information comes in
每当有新信息出现时
whenever new growl releases go out in
每当新的咆哮声发布时
particular we have a very direct line
特别是我们有一条直线
with the garage VM team at Oracle and
与Oracle的车库VM团队一起
there's some very immediate
有一些非常直接的
collaboration with them a lot of our
与他们合作很多
feedback already went integral VM a
反馈已进入虚拟机
recent releases this long released
长期发行的最新版本
candidate face that went through and
经过的候选人脸
there's further feedback of ours that
还有我们的反馈
will make it into upcoming rally and
将使其成为即将到来的集会，
releases soon so by the time that the
即将发布，因此
ground VM team decides to declare its
地面VM团队决定宣布其
native image support as production
支持本机图像作为生产
already which I expect sometime next
我已经期待下一个时间了
year
年
the
的
it's uh-oh they will in all likelihood
恩，哦，他们很可能会
be corresponding guidance from our side
从我们这边得到相应的指导
in terms of what you need to do to
根据您需要做什么
deploy a spring application to to enrich
部署spring应用程序以丰富
a spring application with the
春天的应用
appropriate metadata so that the native
适当的元数据，以便本机
image tool Corral's native image tool
图像工具Corral的本机图像工具
can do the right thing out of the box so
可以开箱即用地做正确的事情
some way to go there and some back and
某种方式去那里，一些回来，
forth between the gravy m and spring
在肉汁m和弹簧之间
engineering groups here but of course a
工程组在这里，但当然
very very attractive option I maybe
我可能非常非常有吸引力的选择
should have even started with why would
本应以为什么开始
you want to do this
你想这样做
well you're building a native image
好吧，您正在构建本机图像
basically a lot of VM infrastructures
基本上有很多VM基础架构
totally cut short a native a native
完全砍掉一个本地人
image of a spring based application can
基于Spring的应用程序的图像可以
bootstrap in total a fraction of a
引导程序总共只有一小部分
second it can use I like a fraction of
第二它可以使用我喜欢的一小部分
the memory that a full JVM based
基于完整JVM的内存
deployment traditional JVM based
部署基于传统JVM的
deployment would use so you would do
部署将使用，所以您会做
this primarily for a very immediate
这主要是非常立即的
startup a very short startup time and
启动时间很短，并且
you would do it for dramatically reduced
你会做的大大减少
memory consumption those would be the
内存消耗将是
two reasons in particular for
特别是两个原因
short-lived processes for cloud
云的短暂过程
deployments with very dynamic starting
动态启动的部署
and stopping of processes this is of
并停止进程
course a very attractive option as it
当然是一个非常有吸引力的选择
materializes for for production purposes
为生产目的而实现
so stay tuned something will be coming
所以请继续关注
in that space some of the immediate
在那个空间里一些直接的
revisions whatever we do make it into
修改我们所做的一切
spring final five third one and five to
春季决赛五分之一三和五
two already so we're trying to ship
已经有两个了，所以我们正在尝试运送
anything we can any refinements we do
我们可以做的任何事情
out of the box but the production level
开箱即用，但生产水平
story very much depends on further grow
故事很大程度上取决于进一步发展
vm releases and production readiness
vm发布和生产就绪
declared on gravity and beside for the
在重力和旁边声明
native image model all right so much for
本机图像模型非常适合
that there's a few implications on the
有一些影响
component model so just to make this
组件模型，只是为了做到这一点
very clear performance tuning is not
非常明显的性能调整不是
totally transparent there so there's
那里完全透明所以
only so much we can do within the
我们只能在
framework to optimize performance for
优化性能的框架
certain certain arrangements
一定的安排
there's some impact on to the way that
会对方式产生一些影响
you declare components you can you can
您声明可以的组件
basically help the framework in doing a
基本上可以帮助框架
better job in terms of startup time
在启动时间方面更好的工作
through explicit registration of
通过明确注册
components avoiding the clasp of the
避免卡扣的组件
scan or including a components index
扫描或包含组件索引
file for that purpose you can declare as
为此，您可以声明为
many beans as possible as lazy in it so
尽可能多的豆子在里面懒
that parts of your applications that
您的应用程序的那部分
might not ever be needed in a short lift
短时间内可能不需要
startup for a particular purpose are not
出于特定目的启动不是
I have a bootstrap
我有一个引导
so there's a lot a lot of help you can
所以有很多帮助您可以
do and at your component level there's
在您的组件级别上
some new options in five to two for
五到两个新的选择
example on configuration classes you can
您可以在配置类上的示例
set proxy beam methods to false which is
将代理光束方法设置为false
basically saying there's no need to
基本上说没有必要
create a CG deep subclass I'm not going
创建一个我不会去的CG深度子类
to call from one Epping method to
从一种Epping方法调用
another admin method I'm not expecting
我没想到的另一个管理方法
the container to intercept those calls
容器来拦截那些调用
I just declare a few innocent and
我只是宣布一些无辜，
independent admin methods with no direct
独立的管理方法，无直接权限
references between each other this is a
彼此之间的引用这是一个
much simpler arrangement no need to
更简单的安排，无需
intercept anything no need to create a
拦截任何东西，无需创建
sigillum subclass for us at runtime in
在运行时为我们提供sigillum子类
particular for a larger set of classes
特别适用于较大的班级
this may seriously impact the overhead
这可能会严重影响间接费用
of class definition on Sodom this is
所多玛的阶级定义
also something that made it into our
也使它成为我们的东西
wrong configuration classes for typical
典型的错误配置类
spring boot deployments in the spring
春季的 spring boot 部署
from a5 to boot to the two arrangement
从a5引导到两个安排
so we are also making some use of this
所以我们也在利用这个
ourselves by the way this is
我们自己就是这样
semantically the same as putting the
在语义上与将
admin methods on just any non
任何非管理员方法
configuration class so this was totally
配置类，所以这完全是
possible before we're calling this light
在我们称这种光之前可能
configuration analysis so 18 methods on
配置分析，因此有18种方法
any other components and without a net
任何其他组件且没有网
configuration stereotype on top would
顶部的配置原型
behave the same way but in order for
行为相同，但为了
this to still be recognizable as a
这仍然可以识别为
configuration element and to be found
配置元素并被发现
when you look for each configuration
当您寻找每种配置时
classes we decided to introduce it as an
我们决定将其介绍为
option as an attribute of configuration
选项作为配置的属性
classes themselves as well along a
自己也沿着
similar line you may choose to use
您可能会选择使用类似的线
interface based proxies if you design
基于接口的代理（如果您设计）
your components
您的组件
to be decorated through interfaces like
通过诸如
service interfaces with no need for the
服务接口，无需
framework to create a target class proxy
创建目标类代理的框架
as it's called this simply means that we
所谓的意思就是说我们
don't need to create the julep
不需要创建julep
subclasses and startup we can use the
子类和启动我们可以使用
Chaney Kay's own traveling reflect proxy
Chaney Kay自己的旅行反映代理
facility instead as long as your proxies
设施，只要您的代理人
only expose interfaces this is a mode of
只公开接口，这是一种模式
operation that the framework always had
框架始终具有的操作
always came with and this becomes a
总是伴随着，这变成了
little more important now if you're
现在，如果您要
trying to optimize for startup time or
尝试优化启动时间或
if you're trying to design an
如果您要设计一个
application for deployment as a native
本机部署的应用程序
image on RAL VM you're much better off
RAL VM上的映像，情况要好得多
in avoiding CG lip subclasses make use
在避免CG嘴唇子类中使用
of the standard JDK facilities instead
代替标准的JDK工具
and it you'll have a much smoother
这样您会更顺畅
experience in those scenarios so that's
在这些情况下的经验，所以
three examples for the kind of lines
线条的三个例子
that we're working towards trying to
我们正在努力尝试
optimize annotation process is
优化注释过程是
considering index arrangements there's
考虑索引的安排
the whole gravia native image topic and
整个gravia本机图像主题和
there's also this shining through with
这也闪耀着
the component model an aspect of of our
组件模型是我们的一个方面
work here this is only going to continue
在这里工作，这只会继续
and some further work I'm sure will
我敢肯定，还有一些进一步的工作
materialize in the five to three time
在五到三倍的时间内实现
frame here all right final section four
框架在这里好，最后第四节
for two days for purposes for this
为此目的两天
presentations purposes is the reactive
演讲的目的是被动的
topic of course Spring Framework five to
当然是Spring Framework的主题五
two is an opportunity for us to kind of
两个是我们机会
have further iteration over our core
在我们的核心上有进一步的迭代
reactive facilities you are certainly
反应设施，您肯定是
aware that the reactive has been a topic
意识到反应式一直是一个话题
we've been talking about it quite a bit
我们一直在谈论它
and this kind of reactive web controller
以及这种反应式Web控制器
is pretty much the model that we
几乎是我们的模型
introduced in fact at all so much
实际上引入了这么多
shouldn't be much of a surprise just
不应该只是一个惊喜
imagine that this is a web controller
想象这是一个Web控制器
with two HTTP mappings to http endpoints
与HTTP端点的两个HTTP映射
one of them for slash users returning
其中之一用于斜线用户返回
this flux of user saying here's
用户说这是
basically a
基本上是
a reactive stream of user elements that
反应性的用户元素流
you can render out to the caller as a
您可以将其呈现给呼叫者
response whenever whenever you're ready
随时准备回应
to do this and the other one has an
为此，另一个有一个
incoming path variable called some
传入路径变量称为some
underlying repository with a mono of
具有单声道的基础存储库
user return value which is basically a
用户返回值，基本上是
set of instructions of how to arrive at
一套如何到达的指示
this user element for the given ID
给定ID的此用户元素
whenever the processing stack is ready
只要处理堆栈准备就绪
to render it out so much for just the
将其渲染得如此之多
basic semantics this is basically the
基本语义这基本上是
five-o state of affairs what we
五点状态
initially introduced is what we call wet
最初介绍的是所谓的湿
flux this is a totally separate web
助焊剂这是一个完全独立的网络
stack highly efficient web stack based
基于高效Web堆栈的堆栈
on reactor on reactor net Ian and and
在反应堆网Ian上的反应堆上，以及
the nettie networking library underneath
下面的nettie网络库
it covers or adapted onto like Tomcat or
它覆盖或改编成类似Tomcat或
jetty or
码头或
undertow as a core container as a core
底层为核心容器为核心
HTTP engine the entire stack is is
整个堆栈的HTTP引擎是
non-blocking of course from top to
从上到下当然不会阻塞
bottom so it doesn't share any of those
底部，因此它不共享任何一个
semantics with the servlet api in
Servlet API中的语义
parallel to that we have the spring web
与此平行的是我们有弹簧网
MVC stack which is still running on on
MVC堆栈仍在运行
on the sea on servlet containers and in
在servlet容器上和在海上
particular on servlet API assumptions so
特别是关于servlet API的假设
within the servlet callback model where
在servlet回调模型中，
you receive a request you own a thread
您收到一个拥有线程的请求
and during the thread you process the
然后在线程中处理
request you write a response and then
要求您写一个回应，然后
you return and release the thread back
您返回并释放线程
to the pool so we have two parallel web
到游泳池，所以我们有两个平行的网络
stacks one of them traditionally
传统上堆叠其中之一
civic-minded one web flex oriented one
公民意识强的人之一
one reactively oriented the twist here
一个反应灵敏的人在这里
is that reactive signatures like this
是这样的反应性签名
like these here mapping methods HTTP
像这里的这些映射方法HTTP
mapping methods returning a reactive
返回反应式的映射方法
streams publisher I actually support it
流发布者，我实际上支持它
to some degree on spring MVC as well in
在某种程度上也对Spring MVC产生了影响
on web flex you have to code all your
在web flex上，您必须编写所有代码
endpoints your entire code with the
使用
reactive strings model on spring MVC you
Spring MVC上的反应性字符串模型
may decide to declare some of those
可能决定宣布其中一些
endpoints the ones that really truly
终结那些真正真实的
benefit from reactive process
从反应过程中受益
with a read of streams publisher so if
阅读流发布者，所以如果
you deploy these kinds of end points to
您将这些端点部署到
spring MVC on the servlet stack we would
在Servlet堆栈上使用Spring MVC
still try to do the best we can we
仍然尽力做到最好
detected you're using reactive streams
检测到您正在使用反应流
publishers here you're calling get users
您要致电的发布者吸引用户
we switch the servlet we switch the
我们切换servlet，我们切换
servlet request as we get it from the
servlet请求，因为我们从
server container - it's a sync mode and
服务器容器-这是一种同步模式，
then we are adapting this async mode of
那么我们将采用这种异步模式
servlet processing to reactive streams
servlet处理反应流
so we are trying to bind your reactive
所以我们试图约束您的反应
stream this flux to the servlet async
流此流量到servlet异步
mode and as the elements materialize we
模式，随着元素的实现，我们
re awakening the the servlet async
重新唤醒servlet异步
requests and writing those elements so
请求并编写这些元素，以便
it's a it's a callback model that the
这是一个回调模型，
server container offers a certain mode
服务器容器提供某种模式
of processing that we can use for in
可以用于
particular for for response elements as
特别适用于响应元素
reactive streams publishes there are
反应流发布有
limitations to this but we're really
限制，但我们确实
taking it very far we're trying to make
到很远，我们正在努力使
everything possible that is technically
从技术上讲一切可能
sensible so you can even have a little
明智的，所以你甚至可以有一点
bit of a reactive streams experience on
反应流的一点点经验
spring MVC on the servlet stack if you
如果您在servlet堆栈上使用Spring MVC
wanted to even more than this there's a
想要的不仅仅是这个
new reactive transaction management
新的被动交易管理
model in Spring Framework 52 it's this
Spring Framework 52中的模型就是这个
is intentionally a very similar example
故意是一个非常相似的例子
imagine that we are not coding a
想象我们没有在编码
controller right now we are building a
控制器，现在我们正在建立一个
service class a little bit of an
服务等级有点
indirection a service facade this one is
间接服务立面这是
very simple initially it just delegates
最初非常简单，只是委托
to an underlying repository and it adds
到基础存储库并添加
a transaction boundary to it it does so
它的交易边界
using the common edge transactional
使用公共边缘事务
model so by just taking methods like
因此，只需采取类似
these here marking them with add
这些在这里用添加标记
transactional and having at enable
事务性的并具有启用功能
transaction management in your
您的交易管理
configuration we would intercept them a
配置，我们将拦截他们
transaction interceptor comes in tries
事务拦截器进入尝试
to intercept those calls but
拦截这些电话，但是
understanding in five to two now that
现在五到两个的理解
these are returning reactive streams
这些正在返回反应流
publishes it doesn't try to naively
发布它不会天真的尝试
intercept them and start a transaction
拦截他们并开始交易
binded to the thread called the method
绑定到称为方法的线程
and then committed and rolling it back
然后提交并回滚
that doesn't make any sense
那没有任何意义
extremes publishers these methods are
极端发布者这些方法是
not actually processing to in the
没有实际处理到
underlying processing these methods
基本处理这些方法
build a pipeline for how to arrive at
建立如何到达的管道
the user objects so there's no point in
用户反对，所以毫无意义
trying to do any kind of threat bound
试图做任何形式的威胁
transactions so we immediately switch
交易，所以我们立即切换
looking at the return type we
看返回类型，我们
immediately switch into the reactive
立即切换到反应式
transaction manager mode of operation we
交易经理的经营方式
are taking the reactive streams
正在采取反应流
publisher coming out of that method we
发布者采用这种方法
are decorating it with a transactional
用交易装饰它
operator this is sort of a a
运算符，这有点
transactional decorator for the
事务装饰器
underlying pipeline this operator puts
该操作员放置的基础管道
transactional elements basically
交易要素
transactional resources and handles into
交易资源和处理
the underlying reactor context so it
基础反应堆环境
always is being turned into a reactor
总是被变成反应堆
flux or mono and we are trying to make
通量或单声道，我们正在努力使
use of a particular reactor feature the
使用特定的反应堆功能
reactor context to store certain
反应堆上下文来存储某些
elements that go with the flow basically
基本上与流程一致的元素
through the reactive pipeline so a
通过反应管道，这样
transactional operator just basically
交易运营商基本上
starts a transaction or actually adds
开始交易或实际添加
and operated it starts a transaction
并操作它开始交易
then this operator would store the idea
然后这个操作员会存储想法
underlying the underlying metadata in
基础元数据的基础
the reactor context and at the very end
反应堆上下文以及最后
of processing it based on the error
基于错误的处理
signal on regular outcome a successful
定期结果成功的信号
completion it would trigger a rollback
完成将触发回滚
or a commit so it does the right thing
或提交，因此它做对了
semantically very intuitive
语义上非常直观
automatically just with the standard a
自动与标准
transactional element and with at the
交易元素，并在
neighbor transaction management being
邻居事务管理
active this needs a particular SPI
活跃的，这需要特定的SPI
implementation so there's a new spi
实施，所以有一个新的SPI
called reactive transaction manager and
称为被动交易经理，
this is an alternative to the good old
这是好旧的替代
platform transaction manager that spring
那年春天的平台交易经理
is traditionally using for thread bound
传统上用于线程绑定
transaction for effort on transaction
为交易而努力
there are currently two implementations
当前有两种实现
for our two DBC our relational reactive
对于我们的两个DBC，我们的关系反应式
relational database connectivity project
关系数据库连接项目
and for MongoDB both of them live in
对于MongoDB，他们两个都住在
Spring data at the moment this may be
当前的Spring数据可能是
revisited at some point but for the time
在某个时候重新访问，但有一段时间
being both of those implement
两者都是
Asians live in spring data so by
亚洲人生活在春季数据中，因此
choosing to use spring format five to
选择使用春季格式五
two and the spring data more released
二，春季数据更多发布
rain you can have the complete
下雨就可以了
experience very quickly there's also a
很快就会有一个
programmatic arrangement you may choose
您可以选择程序安排
to programmatically interact with the
以编程方式与
transaction transactional operator
交易交易运营商
arrangement so instead of doing an
这样安排，而不是做
annotation driven transaction
注释驱动的交易
you may also programatically compose a
您也可以以编程方式撰写
reactive streams publisher that you
您的反应式流发布者
choose to decorate with such a
选择用这样的装饰
transactional operator there's a
交易操作员
programmatic equivalent for it
程序等效
all right so much for reactive
这么好的反应
transactions there's quite a bit of work
交易有很多工作
in the spring messaging module where we
在春季消息传递模块中，我们
basically take the existing messaging
基本上采用现有的消息传递
arrangement arrangement with its message
消息安排
mapping annotation and all of the
映射注释和所有
supporting infrastructure that comes
支持随之而来的基础架构
with it
用它
there is a reactive equivalent for that
有一个等效的反应
infrastructure now for a completely
现在的基础设施
reactive streams based message
基于反应流的消息
interaction model this is primarily used
主要使用的交互模型
with our sockets as mentioned in the
用我们在插座中提到的
keynote this morning so just to give you
今天早上的主题演讲是为了给你
an idea this is programming model wise
这是编程模型明智的想法
very similar message mapping annotations
非常相似的消息映射注释
in within the common spring component
在普通弹簧组件内
model and then different flavors of how
模型，然后是不同口味的
you would express yourself with an
你会用
incoming payload a simple payload coming
传入负载一个简单的负载
in and a reactive streams publisher for
和一个反应式流发布者
the for the response coming coming out
响应出来的
of it
其中
then built into a reactive stack at
然后内置到反应堆中
runtime so totally non-blocking
运行时，因此完全无阻塞
highly efficient processing and very
高效的处理和非常
close to the underlying metal in our
接近我们的基础金属
socket since our socket itself is also
套接字，因为我们的套接字本身也是
reactive stream space this is a very
反应流空间这是一个非常
immediate match there's of course a way
即时比赛当然有办法
of returning a stream of elements and
返回元素流和
there's also a channel mode of operation
还有一种渠道运作模式
according to the our socket model where
根据我们的插座型号
you can have a sequence of elements
你可以有一系列的元素
basically an open-ended stream of
基本上是开放式的
elements coming in and an open-ended
元素进入和开放式
stream going out and you can register a
流出去，您可以注册一个
return a reactive streams publisher that
返回一个反应式流发布者
just does whatever you want
随心所欲
that channel to do in terms of
该渠道要做的
processing those elements so we're the
处理这些元素，所以我们
part that we are doing at Spring
我们在春季所做的部分
Framework level is this immediate and
框架级别是直接的
very natural integration into the spring
非常自然地融入春天
messaging module into the annotation
消息传递模块放入批注
based endpoint model for for spring
基于弹簧的端点模型
messaging that is very similar to what
消息非常类似于
you would use when you were using stomp
当您使用脚踩时会用
on WebSockets for example you're using
例如在WebSockets上使用
the same programming model a little
相同的编程模型
specifically bound of course to the
当然明确地绑定到
stomp protocol but it's fundamentally
脚踩协议，但从根本上讲
the same structure the same
相同的结构相同
configuration elements and wherever
配置元素以及任何地方
possible the same semantics and the same
可能相同的语义和相同的
conversion infrastructure underneath the
下方的转换基础架构
covers so last but not least there is
涵盖了最后但并非最不重要的
also a a plan for revisiting application
也是重新申请的计划
events the application event facility is
事件是应用程序事件工具
a core part of the spring application
弹簧应用程序的核心部分
context arrangements and this
上下文安排和这个
traditionally well it's it's simply in
传统上很好，因为它只是在
its in its semantics as a publish event
它的语义是发布事件
mechanism where the container itself and
容器本身和
some of the integration with the
一些与
container some of the integrated
集装箱一些综合
infrastructure can publish events you
基础架构可以发布事件
may also publish events yourself of
也可能自己发布活动
course programmatically through
以编程方式通过
injecting the application context or its
注入应用程序上下文或其
application in bed publish apart and
床上的申请分开发表
calling publish event on it's there's
在它上调用发布事件
standard events with an event hierarchy
具有事件层次结构的标准事件
that's what we call payload events where
这就是我们所谓的有效负载事件
it's sufficient to just pass in the
只需传递
payload for triggering an events behind
触发事件背后的有效载荷
the infrastructure there's an SPI a
基础设施上有一个SPI
multicast infrastructure for how those
多播基础架构如何
events are going to be dispatched and
事件将被调度，
how they are going to end up in what we
他们将如何最终进入我们的生活
call application listeners the event
呼叫应用程序监听器事件
listener annotation is basically an
侦听器注释基本上是
inert a and annotation based form of
惰性和基于注释的形式
such an application listener
这样的应用程序监听器
traditionally this is just an incoming
传统上，这只是传入
event process it void return value and
事件处理使它的返回值无效，并且
whatever happens right you're not really
不管发生什么事，你不是真的
supposed to do some expensive work here
应该在这里做一些昂贵的工作
you could you could trigger some async
你可以触发一些异步
steps manually from here if you wanted
如果需要，请从此处手动执行步骤
to it's basically just a notification a
基本上只是一个通知
callback signal that that event happened
发生该事件的回调信号
and in a standard set up this code is
在标准设置中，此代码是
actually going to execute within
实际上要在内部执行
the caller's threat so whoever does
呼叫者的威胁，无论谁做
publish event within that threat that
在威胁范围内发布事件
calls publish event all of the listeners
呼叫发布事件所有听众
would run there are configuration
将运行有配置
options options to have a threat pool
拥有威胁池的选项
behind this and so forth but in a
在这个后面等等，但是在
standard arrangement that's pretty much
非常标准的安排
what happens so an idea for m3 or
发生了什么，所以对于m3的想法还是
possibly our c1 still for the 5 to 2
可能我们的c1仍然是5比2
timeframe is that we would allow those
时间表是我们将允许那些
methods to not miss to not necessarily
不要错过不一定的方法
be void here or or declare a return
在此无效或声明退货
event directly but rather use reactive
直接发生事件，而是使用反应性
streams as well like we do in other
流，就像我们在其他地方所做的一样
places an amount of void is basically
放置空隙的数量基本上是
just a completion signal saying oh this
只是完成信号说哦
is actually building erected streams
实际上正在建造直立的溪流
publisher the amount across the police
出版商整个警察的金额
integrates this particular publisher
整合了这个特定的发布者
this particular reactive streams
这种特殊的反应流
pipeline into your pipeline processing
管道进入您的管道处理
so the multicast aura would get a new
所以多播光环会得到一个新的
mode of operation a new understanding of
操作方式的新认识
how to deal with reactive streams
如何处理反应流
publishers that might come from several
可能来自多个发行商
listeners with one listen it's trivial
听众一听就知道
it's more interesting if several
如果有几个更有趣
listeners returned reactive streams
侦听器返回了反应流
publishes and it would then do the right
发布，然后它将做正确的事
thing basically to wrap them up
基本上把它们包起来的东西
efficiently with a reactor processor and
使用反应堆处理器有效地
and execute them behind the scenes in an
并在后台执行它们
asynchronous fashion so by just allowing
异步方式，只需允许
these signatures with a completion
这些签名和完成
signal or with an event to trigger when
发出信号或触发事件
when we are done processing my event
当我们处理完我的活动后
then the publisher would end up
然后发布者最终会
producing and my other event that we
生产和我的其他活动
would finally publish behind the scenes
最终会在幕后发布
whenever it's ready and there's also an
只要准备好，还有
idea of not just allowing to use reactor
不仅允许使用反应堆的想法
for this reactor reactor monotype a real
对于此反应堆，单型为实型
reactive streams publisher with back
带有返回的反应流发布者
pressure support like we do in other
像我们在其他方面一样提供压力支持
places we are also considering to
我们也在考虑的地方
support completable future as a return
支持可完成的未来作为回报
value this is of course the java.util
值，这当然是java.util
concurrent completable feature from java
Java的并发可完成功能
8 you can do this in spring MVC already
8您已经可以在Spring MVC中做到这一点
you can do this in the spring messaging
您可以在春季消息中做到这一点
module already so we figure we could
模块已经存在，所以我们认为我们可以
also support it for the application
也支持它的应用程序
events
大事记
so this is work in progress or design in
所以这是正在进行的工作或正在设计中
progress to be implemented before 5:00
5:00之前要实施的进度
to to our z1 still to spire to add some
到我们的z1仍然想增加一些
spice to the application event facility
应用程序事件工具的香料
and close close a bit of a gap there so
并缩小那里的差距
the underlying infrastructure since I
自我以来的基础设施
just mentioned completely future
刚刚提到完全未来
adaption actually uses an adapter model
适应实际上使用适配器模型
in case you're wondering how we do this
如果您想知道我们如何做到这一点
it all ends up in reactor but if you
全部都放在反应堆中，但是如果你
return and non react the type to us or
返回并且不对我们做出反应
let's put it the other way around if you
让我们换一种说法
return a reactor model or flux to us we
向我们返回反应堆模型或通量
immediately integrate this into our core
立即将其整合到我们的核心
reactive infrastructure directly if you
如果您直接使用反应性基础架构
return something else to us like an Rx
向我们返回其他东西
Java flowable or an arch java single or
Java flowable或Arch Java Single或
if you return a a completable future to
如果您将一个可完成的未来归还给
us then we would try to adapt them to
我们那么我们将尝试使他们适应
the corresponding reactor types for
对应的反应堆类型
completable future we would wrap it with
完整的未来，我们将用
a mono for the archetype of flowable
可流动原型的单声道
type we would wrap it in a flux if you
类型，如果您愿意，我们会将其包装在助焊剂中
return a plane wreck of streams
返回溪流的平面残骸
publisher to us we would also decorate
发布者给我们，我们也会装饰
it with an RA reactor flux accordingly
相应地使用RA反应堆通量
to be able to fully integrate it with
能够与之完全集成
the underlying infrastructure so that
基础基础架构
this happens pretty much underneath the
这几乎发生在
covers it's what we call reactive api
涵盖了我们所谓的反应式API
adaptors interests in case you're
适配器的利益，以防万一
wondering since we were talking about
想知道自从我们在谈论
coughing coroutines this morning this is
今天早上咳嗽协程，这是
also the way that we integrate
也是我们整合的方式
co-routines it's kind of a special
协同例程有点特殊
reactive return type that the coupling
联轴器的无功返回类型
flow type and the coating the third type
流动型和涂料第三型
understood this along the same lines
同样理解这一点
yay suspend function as a spent fund
暂时中止作为已用资金的职能
method in Kotlin naturally returns those
Kotlin中的方法自然会返回那些
basically like a cross in flow and
基本上就像一个十字架
autumn underneath the covers we
在被窝里的秋天
automatically adapted to a reactor flux
自动适应反应堆通量
and process it along the lines of a
并按照
regular reactive streams publisher
常规无功流发布者
integrated with the entire reactive
与整个反应堆集成
infrastructure that spring comes with
春天来的基础设施
alright that's all I had for you today
好了，这就是我今天给你的全部
for this session so we're talking about
在本次会议上，我们正在谈论
a future rate API design topics
未来速率API设计主题
annotation processing huge deal
批注处理
hopefully you won't even notice just a
希望你甚至不会注意到
little bit more efficient in in in
in in的效率更高
processing your annotations but every
处理您的注释，但每
factoring underneath the covers with a
在封面下面加上一个
pretty huge one
相当大的一个
there's the reactive transaction
有被动交易
management model for in particular for
特别是针对
r2 DBC and MongoDB for backends that
r2 DBC和MongoDB用于后端
actually understand half a proper
真正了解一半正确
transaction have proper transaction
交易有适当的交易
semantics that we can attach while being
我们可以在存在时附加的语义
reactive stream spaced there's our
间隔开的反应流
socket messaging integration which is
套接字消息传递集成
the spring messaging module coming with
春天消息模块附带
generic reactive messaging
通用反应式消息传递
infrastructure and particular our socket
基础设施，特别是我们的插座
bindings coming with them and just a
与他们一起的绑定，只是
little bit at the very end we were
在最后一点
referring back to coupling coroutines
回到耦合协程
and the way that they are integrated
以及它们整合的方式
with our underlying reactive api types
与我们的基础反应式API类型
so that's where how they're the big
所以这就是他们很大的地方
common themes connect to the story line
共同的主题连接到故事情节
of this particular session today so
今天这个特别会议的
thanks for your attention i'm of course
谢谢您的关注，我当然
happy to take any questions just come up
很高兴回答任何问题
to the stage we can have any
到舞台上我们可以有任何
conversations about any of those topics
关于任何主题的对话
otherwise just pick me or anyone else
否则就接我或其他人
from the engineering group as you find
从工程组找到
us in the hallways so thanks for your
我们在走廊上，谢谢你
attention enjoy the rest of the show
注意欣赏节目的其余部分
[Applause]
[掌声]
you
您
[Music]
[音乐]